A Guide to the Hao Wang papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA274
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Office Files, 2
  - J.R. Schoenfield (Box 28, Folder 710)
  - J.R. Schoenfield (Box 28, Folder 710A)
  - Scholarly Correspondence (1949-1950), Rosser, Scholz, et. al. (Box 28, Folder 711)
  - Anthony Sholl (Box 28, Folder 712)
  - School and Housing (Box 28, Folder 713)
  - Morris Schreiber (Box 28, Folder 714)
  - Science 85 (Box 28, Folder 715)
  - Science and Technology Review (Box 28, Folder 716)
  - Science in China (Box 28, Folder 717)
  - Science Press (Box 28, Folder 718)
  - "Scientific American" (Box 28, Folder 719)
  - Dana Scott (Box 28, Folder 720)
  - Philip Scott (Box 28, Folder 721)
  - Philip Scott (Box 28, Folder 721A)
  - Frederick Seitz (Box 28, Folder 722)
  - Peter Sellers (Box 29, Folder 723)
  - Warren L. Semon (Box 29, Folder 724)
  - S.G. Shanker (Box 29, Folder 725)
  - Stewart Shapiro (Box 29, Folder 726)
  - Yuting Shen (1 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 727)
  - Yuting Shen (2 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 728)
  - Geoffrey Shephard (Box 29, Folder 729)
  - J.C. Shepherdson (Box 29, Folder 730)
  - Paul Shiman (Box 29, Folder 731)
  - Richard Shore (Box 29, Folder 732)
  - SIAM (Society for Industrial and Applied Mathematics) (Box 29, Folder 733)
  - Jörf Siekman and Graham Wrightson (Box 29, Folder 734)
  - Jack H. Silver (Box 29, Folder 735)
  - Jack H. Silver (Box 29, Folder 735A)
  - John Simms (Box 29, Folder 736)
  - John Simms (Box 29, Folder 736A)
  - M.A. Sinaceur (Box 29, Folder 737)
  - Slippery Rock University (Box 29, Folder 738)
  - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation (Box 29, Folder 739)
  - Tim Smiley (Box 29, Folder 740)
  - C. Smorynski (Box 29, Folder 741)
  - Societies and Books (Box 29, Folder 742)
  - Society of Fellows (Box 29, Folder 743)
  - Robert Solovay (Box 29, Folder 744)
  - Robert Solovay (Box 29, Folder 744A)
  - Peter Sorokin (Box 29, Folder 745)
  - Ernst Specker (Box 29, Folder 746)
  - Donald C. Spencer (Box 30, Folder 747)
  - J.F. Staal (Box 30, Folder 748)
  - Betty Stanton (Box 30, Folder 749)
  - State University of New York at Albany (Box 30, Folder 750)
  - Stechert-Hafner, Inc. (Box 30, Folder 751)
  - M. Stefik (Box 30, Folder 752)
  - Howard Stein (Box 30, Folder 753)
  - Michael Stillman (Box 30, Folder 754)
  - Anne Street (Box 30, Folder 755)
  - "Summary of Issues," December 13, 1965 [re: Harvard University] (Box 30, Folder 756)
  - Domin Svorad (Box 30, Folder 757)
  - Symposium on the Philosophy of Russell (Box 30, Folder 758)
  - Synthese (Box 30, Folder 759)
  - T (Box 30, Folder 760)
  - W.W. Tait (Box 30, Folder 761)
  - Pavol Tarina (Box 30, Folder 762)
  - "Teaching Philosophy" (Box 30, Folder 763)
  - Ralph Teutsch (Box 30, Folder 764)
  - David Thaler (Box 30, Folder 765)
  - Robert Tragesser (Box 30, Folder 766)
  - Leslie H. Tharp (1 of 3) (Box 30, Folder 767)
  - Leslie H. Tharp (Box 30, Folder 767A)
  - Leslie H. Tharp (2 of 3) (Box 30, Folder 768)
  - Leslie H. Tharp (3 of 3) (Box 31, Folder 769)
  - Leslie H. Tharp, Quine Notes (Box 31, Folder 770)
  - Theorems on Equivalence to Semi-Groups (Box 31, Folder 771)
  - Christian Thiel (Box 31, Folder 772)
  - Third World Academy of Sciences (Box 31, Folder 773)
  - Robert Thomas (Box 31, Folder 774)
  - Robert Thomas, Philosophia Mathematica (Box 31, Folder 775)
  - Richard Thompson (Box 31, Folder 776)
  - Lajos Toth (Box 31, Folder 777)
  - Travel Plans, etc. - Kirchberg and Cambridge, August 15 to September 6, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 778)
  - Ji-Lin Tsui (Box 31, Folder 779)
  - J.W. Tucker (University of Waterloo) (Box 31, Folder 780)
  - Tom Tymoczko (Box 31, Folder 781)
  - Wang Tze-sung (Box 31, Folder 782)
  - George Uhlenbeck (Box 31, Folder 783)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 31, Folder 784)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 31, Folder 784A)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 31, Folder 785)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 31, Folder 786)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 31, Folder 787)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 32, Folder 788)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 32, Folder 789)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 32, Folder 790)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 32, Folder 791)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 33, Folder 792)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence, Includes: “Über Einige Satzfunktionen in der Arithmetik” von Th. Skolem (Box 33, Folder 793)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 33, Folder 794)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 33, Folder 795)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 33, Folder 796)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 797)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 798)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 799)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 800)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 801)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence, 1966-1979 (Box 34, Folder 802)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence, 1972-1990 (Box 34, Folder 803)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 35, Folder 804)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 35, Folder 805)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence, 1983-1988 (Box 35, Folder 806)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence, 1985-1994 (Box 35, Folder 807)
  - Unfoldered Correspondence, Hao Wang's Family (Box 35, Folder 808)
  - Unfoldered "Rockefollies" Material (Box 35, Folder 809)
  - Unidentified (Box 35, Folder 810)
  - Unity of Knowledge (Box 35, Folder 811)
  - University of North Carolina, Philosophy of Mathematics Symposium (Box 35, Folder 812)
  - University of Toronto (Box 35, Folder 813)
  - Unlabeled Correspondence (Box 35, Folder 814)
  - Alasdair L.F. Urquhart (Box 35, Folder 815)
  - V (Box 35, Folder 816)
  - Mark van Atten (Box 35, Folder 817)
  - Van Nostrand Reinhold (Box 35, Folder 818)
  - Armando Verdiglione (Box 35, Folder 819)
  - Verlag Kammerer and Unverzagt (Box 35, Folder 820)
  - John von Neumann's Five Illinois Lectures (Box 35, Folder 821)
  - G.H. von Wright (Box 35, Folder 822)
  - W (Box 36, Folder 823)
  - "Wall Street Journal" (Box 36, Folder 824)
  - Hao Wang, Personal (Box 36, Folder 825)
  - Hao Wang, Personal (Box 36, Folder 825A)
  - Zi-Song Wang (Box 36, Folder 826)
  - Michael S. Watanabe (Box 36, Folder 827)
  - Paul Weingartner (Box 36, Folder 828)
  - Scott Weinstein (Box 36, Folder 829)
  - Scott Weinstein (Box 36, Folder 829A)
  - Jerry Weisbach (Director, Technology Transfer) (Box 36, Folder 830)
  - Margaret Wertheim (Box 36, Folder 831)
  - Eduard Wette (Box 36, Folder 832)
  - Wayne Wickelgren (Box 36, Folder 833)
  - Torsten Weisel (Box 36, Folder 834)
  - David S. Wilson (Box 36, Folder 835)
  - Mark Wilson (Box 36, Folder 836)
  - A.J.S. Winter (Box 36, Folder 837)
  - Wissenschaftliche Buchgesellschaft (Box 36, Folder 838)
  - Jan Woleński (Box 36, Folder 839)
  - Zbigniew W. Wolkowski (Box 36, Folder 840)
  - World Congress of Philosophy (Box 36, Folder 841)
  - World Directory of Historians of Mathematics (Box 36, Folder 842)
  - Wen Tsiin Wu (Box 36, Folder 843)
  - Ma Xiwen (Box 36, Folder 844)
  - Zhen Xu (Box 36, Folder 845)
  - Y (Box 36, Folder 846)
  - Mitsuru Yasuhara (Box 36, Folder 847)
  - C.E.M. Yates (Box 36, Folder 848)
  - Angelina Yee (Box 36, Folder 849)
  - Angelina Yee (Box 36, Folder 849A)
  - Chia-Shun Yih (Box 36, Folder 850)
  - Palle Yourgrau (Box 36, Folder 851)
  - Palle Yourgrau (Box 36, Folder 851A)
  - Wu Yunzeng (Box 36, Folder 852)
  - Ivo Zapletal (Box 36, Folder 853)
  - Li Zehou (Box 36, Folder 854)
  - Xiao-Dong Zhou (Box 36, Folder 855)
- Manuscripts, Notes, and Notebooks, 3
  Series 3, Manuscripts, Notes, and Notebooks, is the largest series of material, and is also arranged alphabetically. This series consists of Wang’s notes, various drafts of manuscripts written by Wang (either for an article or book), as well as a set of research notebooks kept by Wang.
  - 1966-1967 (also Kripke Lectures, 1971), 1966-1967, 1971; Includes: “Measurable Cardinals and Analytic Games” by Donald A. Martin “On the Lebesgue Measurability and the Axiom of Determinateness” by Jan Mycielski and S. Świerczkowski “On the Axiom of Determinateness (II)” by Jan Mycielski “The Axiom of Determinateness and Reduction Principles in the Analytical Hierarchy” by Donald A. Martin “General Theory of ∇-Models” by Petr Vopěnka “Forcing á la Solovay” by Jack Silver (Box 37, Folder 856)
  - 1976 and 1977, "Alternative Approaches to Philosophy" (Box 37, Folder 857)
  - 2PM - "Two Pillars of Platonism for Mathematics: Varieties, Choices, Extensions", Includes: “Between Philosophy and Platonism in Mathematics: Discussions with Gödel and Wittgenstein” (Box 37, Folder 858)
  - 89 MC - Main Control, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 859)
  - 90 MC (Main Control), 1990 (Box 37, Folder 860)
  - 91 MC - Main Control, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 861)
  - 91 MC - Main Control, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 862)
  - 91 MC-1 - Main Control, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 863)
  - 92 MC - Main Control, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 864)
  - 92A (Main Control, Continued from 92 and LCF), June 2, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 865)
  - 92B (Continuation of Control 92A), 1992 (Box 38, Folder 866)
  - 92B, Gödel-related (Box 39, Folder 867)
  - 92A, 92B - Main Control, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 868)
  - 93, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 869)
  - 93-Main Control, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 870)
  - 93A (Continuation of 93) - Main Control, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 871)
  - 93A - Main Control, 1993, continued (Box 39, Folder 872)
  - 93B (Continuation of 93) - Main Control, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 873)
  - 93B - Main Control, 1993, continued (Box 39, Folder 874)
  - 93C (Continuation of 93) - Main Control, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 875)
  - 93C - Control, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 876)
  - 94 - Main Control, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 877)
  - 94 - Main Control, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 878)
  - 94A (Continuation of 94) - Main Control, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 879)
  - 94A - Main Control, 1994, continued (Box 40, Folder 880)
  - 94B (Continuation of 94) - Main Control, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 881)
  - 9MC, Main Control, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 882)
  - Stål O. Aanderaa (Box 40, Folder 883)
  - Stål O. Aanderaa (Box 40, Folder 883A)
  - Wilhelm Ackermann (Box 40, Folder 884)
  - Additions and Corrections to "From Mathematics to Philosophy" (Box 41, Folder 885)
  - "After Gödel, After Heyting" and "The Griss-Brouwer Debate on Negation" by Miriam Franchella (Box 41, Folder 886)
  - "Alternative Philosophies" (Quine Conference Version), 1988 (Box 41, Folder 887)
  - "Alternative Philosophies (SL and InA)", 1988 (Box 41, Folder 888)
  - "Analytic Philosophy", 1982; Includes: “Quine’s Logical Ideas and Philosophical Presuppositions in Historical Perspective” “Notes on the Analytic-Synthetic Distinction” (Box 41, Folder 889)
  - AM231, Student Papers, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 890)
  - APC - "Alternative Philosophies and Complementary" and "Aperiodicity and Constraints" (Box 41, Folder 891)
  - "Aperiodicity and Constraints" (Box 41, Folder 892)
  - "Appendix: Gödel on the Ideality of Time" (Box 41, Folder 893)
  - Applied Mathematics 206, Materials and Notes (Box 41, Folder 894)
  - Applied Mathematics 231, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 895)
  - "Applied Mathematics 232, Fall 1966" by Alan Cobham (Box 42, Folder 896)
  - Applied Mathematics 234, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 897)
  - "An Approach to Deciding Quickly Boolean Validity" by Bradford Dunham and Hao Wang (Box 42, Folder 898)
  - "Automata, Nets, and Quantifiers" by Arthur W. Burks and Hao Wang (Box 42, Folder 899)
  - BBS, "On Computabilism and Physicalism: Some Subproblems" (Box 42, Folder 900)
  - Bem Ph Math (allg), Transcribed by Cheryl Dawson, April 1992 [Bemerkungen Philosophie Mathematik (allgemein)] (Box 42, Folder 901)
  - Berkeley, Concept of Mind, 1969; Includes: “Perceptual Illusions and Brain Models” by R.L. Gregory “Philosophy and Computer Simulation” by Keith Gunderson “A Critique of Artificial Reason” by Hubert L. Dreyfus “Visual Illusions” by Richard L. Gregory “The Mental Life of Some Machines” by Hilary Putnam “Mind, Brain, and Humanist Values” by Roger W. Sperry “Mind-Body Identity, A Side Issue?” by Charles Taylor “Behavior, Belief and Emotion” by Alasdair MacIntyre “Brains and Behaviour” by H. Putnam “On How So Little Information Controls So Much Behaviour” by R.L. Gregory (Box 42, Folder 902)
  - "Between Logic and Philosophy: Conversations with Kurt Gödel," Preface, Introduction, and Chapter 1 (Box 42, Folder 903)
  - "Between Logic and Philosophy: Conversations with Kurt Gödel," Chapters 2, 3, and 4 (Box 42, Folder 904)
  - "Between Logic and Philosophy: Conversations with Kurt Gödel," Chapters 5, 6, and 7 (Box 43, Folder 905)
  - "Between Logic and Philosophy: Conversations with Kurt Gödel," Chapters 8, 9, Epilogue and References (Box 43, Folder 906)
  - "Between the Scylla of Scientism and the Charybdis of Apriorism" and "Peirce and Logicism: Notes Towards and Exposition" by Susan Haack (Box 43, Folder 907)
  - "Beyond Analytic Empiricism: Toward Doing Justice to What We Know" (1 of 2) (Box 43, Folder 908)
  - "Beyond Analytic Empiricism: Toward Doing Justice to What We Know" (2 of 2) (Box 43, Folder 909)
  - "Beyond Analytic Empiricism: Toward Doing Justice to What We Know," October 31, 1984 (1 of 2) (Box 44, Folder 910)
  - "Beyond Analytic Empiricism: Toward Doing Justice to What We Know," October 31, 1984 (2 of 2) (Box 44, Folder 911)
  - "Beyond Analytic Philosophy" (1 of 4) (Box 44, Folder 912)
  - "Beyond Analytic Philosophy" (2 of 4) (Box 44, Folder 913)
  - "Beyond Analytic Philosophy" (3 of 4) (Box 45, Folder 914)
  - "Beyond Analytic Philosophy" (4 of 4) (Box 45, Folder 915)
  - "Beyond Analytic Philosophy," Corrections (Box 45, Folder 916)
  - "Beyond Analytic Philosophy" (Correspondence) (Box 45, Folder 917)
  - "Beyond Analytic Philosophy" (Preface, Contents, Introduction) (1 of 2) (Box 46, Folder 918)
  - "Beyond Analytic Philosophy" (Preface, Contents, Introduction) (2 of 2) (Box 46, Folder 919)
  - "Beyond Analytic Philosophy: Doing Justice to What We Know" (1 of 3) (Box 46, Folder 920)
  - "Beyond Analytic Philosophy: Doing Justice to What We Know" (2 of 3) (Box 46, Folder 921)
  - "Beyond Analytic Philosophy: Doing Justice to What We Know" (3 of 3) (Box 46, Folder 922)
  - "Beyond Analytic Philosophy," Chapter 1, "Russell and Philosophy in this Century" (Box 46, Folder 923)
  - "Beyond Analytic Philosophy," Chapter II, "A Digression on Wittgenstein's Philosophy" (Box 47, Folder 924)
  - "Beyond Analytic Philosophy," Chapter III, "From Vienna 1925 to America 1984" (Box 47, Folder 925)
  - "Beyond Analytic Philosophy," Chapter 4, "Quine's Logical Negativism" (Box 47, Folder 926)
  - "Beyond Analytic Philosophy," Chapter 5, "Metaphilosophical Observations" (Box 47, Folder 927)
  - "Beyond Analytic Philosophy" (References and Chronology) (Box 47, Folder 928)
  - BMS, "Between Meaning and Science" (Box 48, Folder 929)
  - BMS, CC, 1989 - "Between Meaning and Science" and "The Concept of Concept" (Box 48, Folder 930)
  - Max Black (Box 48, Folder 931)
  - Max Black (Box 48, Folder 931A)
  - Book MS, 1955-1956 (Box 48, Folder 932)
  - Book Reviews (Box 48, Folder 933)
  - Books and Journals in the Nachlass of Kurt Gödel (Box 49, Folder 934)
  - William Boos (Box 49, Folder 935)
  - "The Calculus of Partial Predicates and its Extension to Set Theory," I (Box 49, Folder 936)
  - "Can Bodies or Computers Be Minds?" (Box 49, Folder 937)
  - "Can Bodies or Computers Have Souls?" (Box 49, Folder 938)
  - "Can Mind do More than Brains?" (Box 49, Folder 939)
  - Cantor's Classification of Sets (Box 49, Folder 940)
  - "A Captious Nicety of Argument: The Philosophy of W.V. Quine" and Notes (Box 49, Folder 941)
  - Richard L. Cartwright, "Ontology and the Theory of Meaning" (Box 49, Folder 942)
  - "Cataloguing the Gödel 'Nachlass'" by John W. Dawson, Jr. (Box 49, Folder 943)
  - CC, "The Concept of Concept" (Box 49, Folder 944)
  - "CG" - Notes and Correspondence on Books on Gödel (Box 49, Folder 945)
  - CG2, 2/7/1991, ("Work as Part of Gödel's Life) (Box 49, Folder 946)
  - CG3, Chapter 2, "The Most Significant Mathematical Truth" (Box 49, Folder 947)
  - CG3 (and CG5), Gödel-related (Box 50, Folder 948)
  - CG4, 4/1/1991, Chapter 2 - "The Separation of Wish and Fact" (Box 50, Folder 949)
  - CG4 - "Separation of Wish and Fact" (Box 50, Folder 950)
  - CG5, 4/1991, Chapter 3, "The Most Significant Mathematical Truth" (Box 50, Folder 951)
  - CG6, 6/10/1991, Chapter 4, "Turing Machines or Gödelian Minds?" (Box 50, Folder 952)
  - CG6 (Turing Machines vs. Gödelian Minds) (Box 50, Folder 953)
  - CGC - Part II - "The Conversations" (Box 51, Folder 954)
  - CG-1, Chapter 1, "Work as Part of Gödel's Life" (Box 51, Folder 955)
  - CGF1, "A Mansion of Many Rooms," Conversations with Kurt Gödel (Box 51, Folder 956)
  - CGF-1, Chapter 1, "A Mansion of Many Rooms" (Box 51, Folder 957)
  - CGF-2 (7/1991), Chapter 2, "The Separation of Wish and Fact" (Box 51, Folder 958)
  - CGF2! - Gödel-related, Includes: “The Separation of Wish and Fact (for Philosophies and Philosophers)” “Kurt Gödel and Phenomenology” by Richard Tieszen (Box 51, Folder 959)
  - Chapter 1, "Gödel's Personal Life and Family Correspondence" (Box 51, Folder 960)
  - Chapter 1, "Three Sketches of Gödel" (Box 52, Folder 961)
  - Chapter 6, "For Perspicuous Objectivity: Realism and Conceptualism" (Box 52, Folder 962)
  - Chapter 7, "Platonism or Objectivism in Mathematics" (Box 52, Folder 963)
  - Chapter 8, What is Philosophy? (Box 52, Folder 964)
  - Chapters 9, 10, and 17, Gödel-related, Includes: “The Nachlass” “Published Thoughts and Delivered Lectures” “Fragments Related to the Conversations” (Box 52, Folder 965)
  - Chapter 11, October 1971 to February 1972 (Box 52, Folder 966)
  - "Chapter S, Sets and Concepts" (Box 52, Folder 967)
  - "The Charm of Set Theory" (Box 52, Folder 968)
  - "The Charm of Set Theory", Includes: “Large Sets” “Notes on Sets and Concepts” “Philosophy through Mathematics and Logic” “Objectivism of Sets and Concepts” “Sets and Concepts” (Box 52, Folder 969)
  - "The Charm of Set Theory" (Box 52, Folder 970)
  - Chinese Typewriters (Box 53, Folder 971)
  - CKG, "Conversations with Kurt Gödel" (Box 53, Folder 972)
  - CKG, 9/1992, "Conversations with Kurt Gödel" (Box 53, Folder 973)
  - CKG1, Chapter 1, "Gödel's Life" (9/1992), "Conversations with Kurt Gödel" (Box 53, Folder 974)
  - CKG1, Chapter 1, "Gödel's Life", 1992 (Box 53, Folder 975)
  - CKG2, 11/3/1992, Chapter 2, "Conversations with Kurt Gödel" (Box 53, Folder 976)
  - CKG2, Chapter 2, "Gödel's Mental Development", 1992 (Box 53, Folder 977)
  - CKG3 - Chapter 3, "The Gap between Wish and Fact," "Conversations with Kurt Gödel" (Box 53, Folder 978)
  - CKG-4, January 6, 1993, Chapter 4, "The Conversations and their Background," "Conversations with Kurt Gödel" (Box 54, Folder 979)
  - CKG5, 3/32/1993, "Purity of Mind: Logic and Gödel to Philosophy," "Conversations with Kurt Gödel" (Box 54, Folder 980)
  - CKG6, 3/16/1993, "The Charm of Set Theory," "Conversations with Kurt Gödel" (Box 54, Folder 981)
  - "CKH/CFH Head of Final Version, CKG", Includes: Review by Thomas Tymoczko, “Computation, Logic, Philosophy: A Collection of Essays” by Hao Wang “Purity of Mind through Logic: On Wittgenstein, Gödel and Ideals of Philosophy” (Box 54, Folder 982)
  - Clarendon Press (Box 54, Folder 983)
  - "Comments on Wang, 'Gödel the Philosopher'" by Charles Parsons (Box 54, Folder 984)
  - "Complexity as Thermodynamic Depth" by Seth Lloyd and Heinz Pagels (Box 54, Folder 985)
  - "Computation, Logic, Philosophy: A Collection of Essays" (Box 54, Folder 986)
  - "Computer Theorem Proving and Artificial Intelligence" (Box 54, Folder 987)
  - "The Concept of Practice (Praxis)" and "Philosophy's Despair" (Box 54, Folder 988)
  - "The Concept of Set" (Box 54, Folder 989)
  - Concept of Set - Chapter VI from "From Mathematics to Philosophy" (Box 54, Folder 990)
  - "Contemporary Chinese Culture: Structure and Emotionality" by Dr. Lung-kee Sun (Box 54, Folder 991)
  - The Continuum (Box 54, Folder 992)
  - "The Contraction of Philosophy from Russell to Quine," Handscript (1 of 2) (Box 55, Folder 993)
  - "The Contraction of Philosophy from Russell to Quine," Handscript (2 of 2) (Box 55, Folder 994)
  - "The Contraction of Philosophy from Russell to Quine" (First Typescript) (Box 55, Folder 995)
  - "Control of Gödel Book", 1985-1986 (Box 55, Folder 996)
  - The Conversations, Gödel-related (Box 56, Folder 997)
  - Conversations..."Einstein and Gödel: Contrast and Friendship" (Box 56, Folder 998)
  - Conversations...RC. "Reminders for Conversations" (Box 56, Folder 999)
  - Conversations...Reminders (Box 56, Folder 1000)
  - Conversations...Chapter 1, "Gödel's Personal Life and Family Correspondence" (Box 56, Folder 1001)
  - Conversations...Chapter 8, "What is Philosophy?" (Box 56, Folder 1002)
  - Conversations...Chapter 11, October 1971 to February 1972, October 1971-February 1972 (Box 56, Folder 1003)
  - Conversations...Chapter 12, March to December 1972, March-December 1972 (Box 56, Folder 1004)
  - Conversations...Chapter 13, October 1975 to January 1976, October 1975-January 1976 (Box 56, Folder 1005)
  - Conversations, Chapter 14, February to June 1976, February-June 1976 (Box 56, Folder 1006)
  - Conversations, Chapter 17, "Fragments Related to the Conversations" (Box 56, Folder 1007)
  - Conversations...Chapter L (Old Chapter 2), "Kurt Gödel, a Life of the Mind (a sketch)" (Box 57, Folder 1008)
  - Conversations...Chapter M, "Mind, Matter, Concept" (Box 57, Folder 1009)
  - Conversations, Chapter N-11, October 1971 to February 1972, October 1971-February 1972 (Box 57, Folder 1010)
  - Conversations, Chapter N-12, March to December 1972, March-December 1972 (Box 57, Folder 1011)
  - Conversations...Chapter S, "Sets and Concepts" (Box 57, Folder 1012)
  - "Conversations with Kurt Gödel, A Fragment on Philosophy and Math" (Box 57, Folder 1013)
  - "Conversations with Kurt Gödel," Part II (Box 57, Folder 1014)
  - "Conversations with Kurt Gödel," Table of Contents (tentative) (Box 57, Folder 1015)
  - Correspondence re: Gödel (Box 57, Folder 1016)
  - Courses at Harvard (1 of 2), 1961-1966 (Box 57, Folder 1017)
  - Courses at Harvard (2 of 2), 1961-1966 (Box 57, Folder 1018)
  - Cover and Front Matter, "Popular Lectures on Mathematical Logic" (Box 58, Folder 1019)
  - Paul F. Cranefield, Includes: “Robert Bunsen, Carl Ludwig and Scientific Philosophy” by P.F. Cranefield “The Philosophical and Cultural Interests of the Biophysics Movement of 1847” by Paul F. Cranefield “Freud and the School of Helmholtz” by Paul F. Cranefield “Josef Breuer’s Evaluation of his Contribution to Psycho-Analysis” by Paul F. Cranefield “Breuer, Josef,” Dictionary of Scientific Biography by Paul F. Cranefield “Some Problems in Writing the History of Psychoanalysis” by Paul F. Cranefield “The Nineteenth-Century Prelude to Modern Biophysics” by Paul F. Cranefield “The Organic Physics of 1847 and the Biophysics of Today” by Owsei Temkin “The Philosophical Background of Magendie’s Physiology” by Owsei Temkin “Science and Empire: East Coast Fever in Rhodesia and the Transvaal” by Paul F. Cranefield (Box 58, Folder 1020)
  - Critical Notice: Michael Dummett, "Frege: Philosophy of Mathematics" by William Demopoulos (Box 58, Folder 1021)
  - [∀∃∀] (Decidable Subcases, Undecidable Subcases, Reduction) (Box 58, Folder 1022)
  - "The Decision Problem for Quantification Theory: The Method of Sequential Tables" by C. Ward Henson III, 1962 (Box 59, Folder 1023)
  - "Decision Procedures, Proof Procedures, and Semidecision Procedures" [Abstract] (Box 59, Folder 1024)
  - R. Dedekind (Box 59, Folder 1025)
  - Michael Detlefsen (Box 59, Folder 1026)
  - DGW1 - "Between Logic and Philosophy" (Box 59, Folder 1027)
  - DGW1 - "The Most Significant Mathematical Truth" (Box 59, Folder 1028)
  - DGW-2, 1/1992 - "Computation and Its Limits" (Box 59, Folder 1029)
  - DGW2, "The Most Significant Mathematical Truth", Includes: “Computation and Its Limits” (Box 59, Folder 1030)